{
    "id": "68_Politics_565",
    "claim": "Morena, PT and PES achieved  millions of votes, % of the total; Together we will make history won  seats in the countryAmong the deputies who would enter for Morena stand Gerardo Fernández Noroña, Sergio Mayer, Dolores Padierna, Mario Delgado and Alfonso Ramírez Cuellar. [email protected] The overwhelming vote that Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador achieved in the presidential election, will reach him to have majorities in the Chamber of Deputies and the Senate of the Republic. By calculating % of the minutes for the election of the Chamber of Deputies in the Preliminary Election Results Program (PREP), the Morena, Labor (PT) and Social Encounter (PES) parties achieved a vote of  million votes (%), while the coalition For Mexico to the Front  made up of the National Action (PAN) parties of the Democratic Revolution (PRD) and Citizens' Movement (MC) obtained  millions  a thousand votes (%), while the All for Mexico alliance  made up of the Institutional Revolutionary Parties (PRI), Green Ecologist of Mexico (PVEM) and New Alliance (NA) reached the million a thousand votes (%). With this, the alliance that ran for Lopez Obrador won  districts, which equals the same number of deputies of relative majority; the PAN, PRD and MC, became  districts and the PRI, PVEM and NA, stayed with  districts. In the party vote, Morena is profiled to be the first force in San Lázaro, with  million  a thousand votes (%); the PAN would follow him with  million  a thousand (%); thirdly the PRI, with  million  a thousand (%); fourth, PRD (%); fifth, PVEM (%); then MC (%); seventh, PT (%); eighth, NA (%) and lastly, PES (%). Majority deputies. According to the list of deputies who would enter for Morena are: Gerardo Fernández Noroña, Sergio Mayer, Dolores Padierna, Mario Delgado, Alfonso Ramírez Cuellar, Aleida Alavez and Zoe Robledo, among others. Some of those who would stay outside would be comedian Ausencio Cruz and panista Mariana Gomez del Campo, among others. It is still necessary to calculate the legislators that each party would obtain through the multi-nominal route, which will have to be for the vote that they reach. For the Senate, Morena, PES and PT won  states in conjunction with a total vote of %; PAN, PRD and MC won in seven with a percentage of %, and the PRI, PVEM and NA won an entity and this represents % of the vote. Lopez Obrador's coalition won * NUMBER* millions * NUMBER* a thousand votes; the coalition For Mexico to the Front reached * NUMBER* millions * NUMBER* a thousand votes; and the alliance that ran for Jose Antonio Meade reached * NUMBER* millions * NUMBER* a thousand votes. According to the first projections of the results of the PREP, Morena's bench would be joined by national political figures such as Nestora Salgado, Martí Batres, Alejandro González Yáñez, Martha Lucía Micher, Felix Salgado Macedonio, Delfina Gomez, Higinio Martínez, Lily Tellez, Alfonso Durazo and Rocío Nahle, among others. Through the multi-nominal route they would have seats Napoleon Gomez Urrutia, Germán Martínez, Ricardo Mon- real, Olga Sánchez Cordero and Ifigenia Martínez. They would also be inside the Front, Gustavo Madero, Gina Cruz, Emilio Álvarez Icaza, Clemente Castañeda, Juan Zepeda, Guadalupe Murguía and Minerva Hernández. In a first review they would be left out by the principle of relative majority, Xochitl Gálvez, Guillermo Anaya, María Elena Orantes, Beatriz Mojica, Guadalupe Acosta Naranjo and Anaya Rosa Payán. Independent Pedro Kumamoto and Manuel J. Clouthier wouldn't come in either. For the PRI, PVEM and NA would enter the Senate, the daughter of Manlio Fabio Beltrones Rivera, Sylvana Beltrones, Manuel Añorve and Jorge Carlos Ramírez Marin. Those who would be outside by the principle of relative majority would be the actress, Leticia Calderon (Green), Beatriz Pages, Jose Reyes Baeza and Cesar Camacho Quiroz. For the Senate of the Republic it is also necessary to calculate the trends to define the multi-nominal seats that each political party would obtain. I'm sorry.",
    "source": "www.eluniversal.com.mx",
    "date": "03/07/2018",
    "veracity": 1,
    "claims": [
        {
            "claim": "Morena, PT and PES Morena  millions of votes, % of the total; Morena's Morena, PT and PES will make history won  seats in the the PAN the deputies who would enter for Morena stand Gerardo the PRI Noroña, Sergio Mayer, Dolores Padierna, Mario Delgado PVEM Alfonso MC Cuellar.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who will make history won seats in the PAN?",
                    "answer": "Morena, PT and PES"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many votes did Morena get for PES Morena?",
                    "score": 0.7482,
                    "answers": "for Morena|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "PT protectedNA The overwhelming vote that Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador achieved in the Morena's election, will Morena Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador to have majorities in the Chamber of Deputies and the Senate of the Republic.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.eluniversal.com.mx report that PT protectedNA?",
                    "answer": "03/07/2018"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who will have majorities in the Chamber of Deputies and the Senate of the Republic?",
                    "answer": "Morena Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many votes did Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador win in the Morena election?",
                    "score": 0.8861,
                    "answers": "www.eluniversal.com.mx reported on 03/07/2018 that PT protectedNA|ROOT"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "By calculating % of the minutes for the election of the Chamber of Deputies in the Preliminary Election Results Program (PREP), Morena, PT and PES achieved a vote of  million votes (%), while the coalition each party to the Front  made up of the National Action (PAN) parties of the Democratic Revolution (PRD) and Citizens' Movement Morena MC) obtained  millions  a thousand votes (%), while the All for the PAN PRD  made up of the Institutional Revolutionary Parties (PRI) the Senate the PRI PVEM the Institutional Revolutionary Parties (PRI) , NA Green Ecologist of Mexico (PVEM) and New Alliance (NA him million a thousand votes (%).",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the All for the PAN PRD made up of?",
                    "answer": "Institutional Revolutionary Parties (PRI) the Senate the PRI PVEM the Institutional Revolutionary Parties (PRI)"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many votes did Morena, PT, and PES receive in the 2018 election?",
                    "score": 0.5635,
                    "answers": "of the National Action ( PAN ) parties of the Democratic Revolution ( PRD ) and Citizens ' Movement Morena MC )|prep\tthe Democratic Revolution ( PRD ) and Citizens ' Movement Morena MC )|pobj\twhile the coalition each party to the Front   made up of the National Action ( PAN ) parties of the Democratic Revolution ( PRD ) and Citizens ' Movement Morena MC ) obtained|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many votes were received in the election of the Chamber of Deputies?",
                    "score": 0.5614,
                    "answers": "and|cc\tmillion votes ( % ) ,|pobj\teach|det\tand|cc\tmillions|nsubj\tthe Senate the PRI PVEM|appos\tand|cc\thim million a thousand votes|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What party received the most votes in the election in 2018?",
                    "score": 0.5399,
                    "answers": "the PRI PVEM|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the Institutional Revolutionary Parties (PRI)?",
                    "score": 0.5398,
                    "answers": "the Institutional Revolutionary Parties ( PRI ) the Senate the PRI PVEM the Institutional Revolutionary Parties ( PRI ) ,|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "With this, Morena, PT and PES won  districts, which equals the same number of deputies of relative majority; the National Action (PAN) , the Democratic Revolution (PRD) and MC, became  districts the Senate , stayed with  districts.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What was the name of the group that won districts in the Senate?",
                    "answer": "the National Action (PAN)"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many deputies did Morena, PT, and PES have in 2018?",
                    "score": 0.7248,
                    "answers": "the same number of deputies of relative majority|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many deputies were deputies of relative majority in the districts in 2018?",
                    "score": 0.6914,
                    "answers": "deputies of relative majority|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many deputies are in the PES district?",
                    "score": 0.6758,
                    "answers": "  districts , which equals the same number of deputies of relative majority|dep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In the party vote, Morena is profiled to be the first force in San Lázaro, with  million  a thousand votes (%); the PAN would follow him with  million  a thousand (%); thirdly the PRI, with  million  a thousand (%); fourth, PRD (%); fifth, PVEM (%); then MC (%); seventh, PT (%); eighth, NA (%) and lastly, PES (%).",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What party would follow Morena with million a thousand votes?",
                    "answer": "PAN"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many votes did Morena receive in San Lázaro in 2018?",
                    "score": 0.7482,
                    "answers": "www.eluniversal.com.mx reported on 03/07/2018 that In the party vote , Morena is profiled to be the first force in San Lázaro , with|ROOT\ton 03/07/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tthe|det\tparty|compound\tthe party vote|pobj\t,|punct\tis|auxpass\tto|aux\tthe|det\tin San Lázaro|prep\tSan|compound\t,|punct\twith|prep\t  million   a thousand votes ( % ) ; the PAN would follow him with   million   a thousand ( % ) ; thirdly the PRI , with   million   a thousand ( % ) ; fourth , PRD ( % ) ; fifth , PVEM ( % ) ; then MC ( % ) ; seventh , PT ( % ) ; eighth , NA ( % ) and lastly , PES ( % )|dep\tmillion|nsubj\tmillion  |dep\ta|quantmod\ta thousand|nummod\tmillion   a thousand votes ( % ) ; the PAN would follow him with   million   a thousand ( % ) ; thirdly the PRI , with   million   a thousand ( % ) ; fourth , PRD ( % ) ; fifth , PVEM ( % ) ; then MC ( % ) ; seventh , PT ( % ) ; eighth , NA ( % ) and lastly , PES ( % )|pobj\t( %|punct\t%|punct\t)|punct\t;|punct\tthe|det\tthe PAN|nsubj\twould|aux\t; the PAN would follow him with   million   a thousand ( % ) ; thirdly the PRI , with   million   a thousand ( % ) ; fourth , PRD ( % ) ; fifth , PVEM ( % ) ; then MC ( % ) ; seventh , PT ( % ) ; eighth , NA ( % ) and lastly , PES ( % )|conj\thim|dobj\twith|prep\t |dep\tmillion|nummod\t |dep\ta|det\t  million   a thousand|dobj\t(|punct\t%|punct\t)|punct\t;|punct\tthe|det\tthirdly the PRI , with   million   a thousand ( % ) ; fourth , PRD ( % ) ; fifth , PVEM ( % ) ; then MC ( % ) ; seventh , PT ( % ) ; eighth , NA ( % ) and lastly , PES ( % )|conj\t,|punct\twith|prep\t |dep\t |dep\ta|det\t  a thousand|quantmod\t(|punct\t%|punct\t)|punct\t;|punct\t,|punct\tfourth , PRD ( % ) ; fifth , PVEM ( % ) ; then MC ( % ) ; seventh , PT ( % ) ; eighth , NA ( % ) and lastly , PES ( % )|conj\t(|punct\t%|punct\t)|punct\t;|punct\t,|punct\tfifth , PVEM ( % ) ; then MC ( % ) ; seventh , PT ( % ) ; eighth , NA ( % ) and lastly , PES ( % )|conj\t(|punct\t%|punct\t)|punct\t;|punct\tthen|advmod\t(|punct\t%|punct\t)|punct\t;|punct\t,|punct\tseventh , PT ( % ) ; eighth , NA ( % ) and lastly , PES ( % )|conj\t(|punct\t%|punct\t)|punct\t;|punct\t,|punct\teighth , NA ( % ) and lastly , PES ( % )|conj\t(|punct\t%|punct\t)|punct\tand|cc\t,|punct\tlastly , PES ( % )|conj\t(|punct\t%|punct\t)|punct"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who was the first force in San Lázaro?",
                    "score": 0.6786,
                    "answers": "the first force in San Lázaro|attr"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Majority deputies.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What was reported on 03/07/2018 by www.eluniversal.com.mx?",
                    "answer": "Majority deputies"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many deputies are there in Canada?",
                    "score": 0.8714,
                    "answers": "www.eluniversal.com.mx|nsubj\ton 03/07/2018|prep\tMajority|compound\tthat Majority deputies|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the number of deputies in Canada in 2018?",
                    "score": 0.8216,
                    "answers": "www.eluniversal.com.mx reported on 03/07/2018 that Majority deputies|ROOT"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "According to the list of deputies who would enter for Morena are: Gerardo Fernández Noroña, Sergio Mayer, Dolores Padierna, Mario Delgado, Alfonso Ramírez Cuellar, Aleida Alavez and Zoe Robledo, among others.",
            "question_answers": [],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the list of deputies who would enter Morena?",
                    "score": 0.75,
                    "answers": "www.eluniversal.com.mx reported on 03/07/2018 that According to the list of deputies who would enter for Morena are : Gerardo Fernández Noroña , Sergio Mayer , Dolores Padierna , Mario Delgado , Alfonso Ramírez Cuellar , Aleida Alavez and Zoe Robledo , among others|ROOT\tthat|mark\tthe|det\twho|nsubj\twould|aux\t:|punct\tGerardo|compound\tFernández|compound\t,|punct\tSergio|compound\tSergio Mayer , Dolores Padierna , Mario Delgado , Alfonso Ramírez Cuellar , Aleida Alavez and Zoe Robledo , among others|conj\t,|punct\tDolores|compound\t,|punct\tMario|compound\tMario Delgado , Alfonso Ramírez Cuellar , Aleida Alavez and Zoe Robledo|conj\t,|punct\tAlfonso|compound\tAlfonso Ramírez Cuellar , Aleida Alavez and Zoe Robledo|conj\t,|punct\tAleida|compound\tand|cc\tZoe|compound\t,|punct\tamong others|prep\tothers|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Some of those who would stay outside would be comedian Ausencio Cruz and panista Mariana Gomez del Campo, among others.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Along with panista Mariana Gomez del Campo, what was Ausencio Cruz's profession?",
                    "answer": "comedian"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is Ausencio Cruz's career?",
                    "score": 0.737,
                    "answers": "comedian|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Ausencio Cruz and Mariana Gomez del Campo's relationship?",
                    "score": 0.7334,
                    "answers": "who would stay outside|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is Mariana Gomez del Campo?",
                    "score": 0.7247,
                    "answers": "Mariana|compound\tGomez|compound\tpanista Mariana Gomez del Campo ,|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many people would stay outside if they were allowed to stay outside?",
                    "score": 0.707,
                    "answers": "of those who would stay outside|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is Ausencio Cruz?",
                    "score": 0.6712,
                    "answers": "comedian Ausencio Cruz and panista Mariana Gomez del Campo , among others|attr"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "It is still necessary to calculate the legislators that each party would obtain through the multi-nominal route, which will have to be for the vote that they reach.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is it still necessary to do to calculate the legislators that each party would obtain through the multi-nominal route?",
                    "answer": "calculate the legislators that each party would obtain through the multi-nominal route,"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does it take to calculate the number of legislators that each party would obtain through the multi-nominal route?",
                    "score": 0.7676,
                    "answers": "that they reach|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the voting process for the 2018 election?",
                    "score": 0.7553,
                    "answers": "www.eluniversal.com.mx reported on 03/07/2018 that It is still necessary to calculate the legislators that each party would obtain through the multi - nominal route , which will have to be for the vote that they reach|ROOT\tthat each party would obtain through the multi - nominal route , which will have to be for the vote that they reach|relcl\tthrough the multi - nominal route , which will have to be for the vote that they reach|prep\twhich will have to be for the vote that they reach|relcl\tto be for the vote that they reach|xcomp\tfor the vote that they reach|prep\tthe vote that they reach|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many votes must be made for each party to obtain to get to the vote?",
                    "score": 0.7337,
                    "answers": "the legislators that each party would obtain through the multi - nominal route , which will have to be for the vote that they reach|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of the \"multi-nominal route\"?",
                    "score": 0.6382,
                    "answers": "the multi - nominal route , which will have to be for the vote that they reach|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "For the Senate, Morena, PES and PT won  states in conjunction with a total vote of %; PAN, PRD and MC won in seven with a percentage of %, and the PRI, PVEM and NA won an entity and this represents % of the vote.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who won in seven states with a percentage of %?",
                    "answer": "PAN, PRD and MC won in seven with a percentage of %,"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many votes did PES and PES receive in the 2018 election?",
                    "score": 0.6749,
                    "answers": "PES and PT|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the percentage of votes needed to win the election?",
                    "score": 0.6136,
                    "answers": "in seven|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the total vote for the Senate in 2018?",
                    "score": 0.5986,
                    "answers": "www.eluniversal.com.mx reported on 03/07/2018 that For the Senate , Morena , PES and PT won   states in conjunction with a total vote of % ; PAN , PRD and MC won in seven with a percentage of % , and the PRI , PVEM and NA won an entity and this represents % of the vote|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the voting record of each state for the Senate, Morena, PES, and PT?",
                    "score": 0.5598,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tthe|det\t,|punct\t,|punct\tand|cc\ta|det\t;|punct\t,|punct\tand|cc\ta|det\t,|punct\tand|cc\tthe|det\t,|punct\tand|cc\tan|det\tand|cc\tthis|nsubj\tthe|det"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Lopez Obrador's coalition won * NUMBER* millions * NUMBER* a thousand votes; the coalition For Mexico to the Front reached * NUMBER* millions * NUMBER* a thousand votes; and the alliance that ran for Jose Antonio Meade reached * NUMBER* millions * NUMBER* a thousand votes.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What coalition reached * NUMBER* millions * NUMBER* a thousand votes?",
                    "answer": "For Mexico to the Front"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many votes did Lopez Obrador win?",
                    "score": 0.7249,
                    "answers": "www.eluniversal.com.mx reported on 03/07/2018 that Lopez Obrador 's coalition won * NUMBER * millions * NUMBER * a thousand votes ; the coalition For Mexico to the Front reached * NUMBER * millions * NUMBER * a thousand votes ; and the alliance that ran for Jose Antonio Meade reached * NUMBER * millions * NUMBER * a thousand votes|ROOT"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "According to the first projections of the results of the PREP, Morena's bench would be joined by national political figures such as Nestora Salgado, Martí Batres, Alejandro González Yáñez, Martha Lucía Micher, Felix Salgado Macedonio, Delfina Gomez, Higinio Martínez, Lily Tellez, Alfonso Durazo and Rocío Nahle, among others.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who was Roco Nahle a member of?",
                    "answer": "Alfonso Durazo"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What political figures have joined Morena's bench?",
                    "score": 0.7437,
                    "answers": "national|amod\tpolitical|amod\tNestora|compound\tMartí|compound\tAlejandro|compound\tMartha|compound\tLucía|compound\tFelix Salgado Macedonio , Delfina Gomez , Higinio Martínez , Lily Tellez , Alfonso Durazo and Rocío Nahle ,|conj\tDelfina Gomez , Higinio Martínez , Lily Tellez , Alfonso Durazo and Rocío Nahle ,|conj\tAlfonso Durazo and Rocío Nahle ,|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What political figures would join Morena's bench?",
                    "score": 0.7293,
                    "answers": "the PREP|pobj\tMorena 's|poss\tGonzález|compound\tDelfina|compound\tHiginio|compound\tRocío|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What political figures are joining Morena's bench?",
                    "score": 0.7219,
                    "answers": "Alfonso|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many political figures would be added to Morena's bench after the results of the PREP?",
                    "score": 0.5908,
                    "answers": "www.eluniversal.com.mx reported on 03/07/2018 that According to the first projections of the results of the PREP , Morena 's bench would be joined by national political figures such as Nestora Salgado , Martí Batres , Alejandro González Yáñez , Martha Lucía Micher , Felix Salgado Macedonio , Delfina Gomez , Higinio Martínez , Lily Tellez , Alfonso Durazo and Rocío Nahle , among others|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of Morena's bench?",
                    "score": 0.5564,
                    "answers": "Morena 's bench|nsubjpass"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Through the multi-nominal route they would have seats Napoleon Gomez Urrutia, Germán Martínez, Ricardo Mon- real, Olga Sánchez Cordero and Ifigenia Martínez.",
            "question_answers": [],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many seats did Eluniversal.com have?",
                    "score": 0.7835,
                    "answers": "www.eluniversal.com.mx|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the website that they are using to announce their candidacy?",
                    "score": 0.7683,
                    "answers": "on 03/07/2018|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many seats were available in the multi-nominal route in 2018?",
                    "score": 0.7458,
                    "answers": "-|amod\t,|punct\t,|punct\t,|punct"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the names of the seats Napoleon Gomez Urrutia, Germán Martínez, and Ricardo Mon- real?",
                    "score": 0.7361,
                    "answers": "would|aux"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Ifigenia Martínez's political affiliation?",
                    "score": 0.7186,
                    "answers": "Ifigenia|compound"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "They would also be inside the Front, Gustavo Madero, Gina Cruz, Emilio Álvarez Icaza, Clemente Castañeda, Juan Zepeda, Guadalupe Murguía and Minerva Hernández.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did www.eluniversal.com.mx report that Gustavo Madero, Gina Cruz, Emilio lvarez Icaza, Clemente Castaeda, Juan Zepeda, Guadalupe Murgua and Minerva Hernández would also be inside the Front?",
                    "answer": "03/07/2018"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Gina Cruz and Fidel Castro?",
                    "score": 0.7599,
                    "answers": "Gina|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the group that Gustavo Madero, Gina Cruz, and Emilio Castañeda belong to?",
                    "score": 0.7485,
                    "answers": "Clemente|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the names of the members of the Front?",
                    "score": 0.7333,
                    "answers": "Emilio Álvarez Icaza , Clemente Castañeda , Juan Zepeda , Guadalupe Murguía and Minerva Hernández|conj\tJuan Zepeda , Guadalupe Murguía and Minerva Hernández|conj\tMinerva|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the link between Fideluniversal and the Front?",
                    "score": 0.6875,
                    "answers": "www.eluniversal.com.mx|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In a first review they would be left out by the principle of relative majority, Xochitl Gálvez, Guillermo Anaya, María Elena Orantes, Beatriz Mojica, Guadalupe Acosta Naranjo and Anaya Rosa Payán.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who was left out of the first review by the principle of relative majority?",
                    "answer": "Guadalupe Acosta Naranjo"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is Guadalupe's principle of relative majority?",
                    "score": 0.6633,
                    "answers": "Guadalupe|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between the principle of relative majority and Xochitl Gálvez and Guillermo Anaya?",
                    "score": 0.6172,
                    "answers": "out|prt"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is Guillermo Anaya?",
                    "score": 0.6063,
                    "answers": "Guillermo|compound"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Independent Pedro Kumamoto and Manuel J. Clouthier wouldn't come in either.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who didn't come in?",
                    "answer": "Pedro Kumamoto and Manuel J. Clouthier"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Pedro Kumamoto and Manuel J. Clouthier?",
                    "score": 0.8547,
                    "answers": "Pedro|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the relationship between Kumamoto and Clouthier?",
                    "score": 0.7846,
                    "answers": "www.eluniversal.com.mx reported on 03/07/2018 that Independent Pedro Kumamoto and Manuel J. Clouthier would n't come in either|ROOT\ton 03/07/2018|prep\tthat|mark\tIndependent|compound\tIndependent Pedro Kumamoto and Manuel J. Clouthier|nsubj\tand|cc\tManuel|compound\tJ.|compound\twould|aux\tn't|neg\tthat Independent Pedro Kumamoto and Manuel J. Clouthier would n't come in either|ccomp\tin|advmod\teither|advmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What iseluniversal.com.mx?",
                    "score": 0.7017,
                    "answers": "www.eluniversal.com.mx|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "For the PRI, PVEM and NA would enter the Senate, the daughter of Manlio Fabio Beltrones Rivera, Sylvana Beltrones, Manuel Añorve and Jorge Carlos Ramírez Marin.",
            "question_answers": [],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Who is the daughter of Manlio Fabio Beltrones Rivera?",
                    "score": 0.7347,
                    "answers": "www.eluniversal.com.mx reported on 03/07/2018 that For the PRI , PVEM and NA would enter the Senate , the daughter of Manlio Fabio Beltrones Rivera , Sylvana Beltrones , Manuel Añorve and Jorge Carlos Ramírez Marin|ROOT\tthe Senate , the daughter of Manlio Fabio Beltrones Rivera , Sylvana Beltrones , Manuel Añorve and Jorge Carlos Ramírez Marin|dobj\tthe daughter of Manlio Fabio Beltrones Rivera , Sylvana Beltrones , Manuel Añorve and Jorge Carlos Ramírez Marin|appos\tBeltrones|compound\tSylvana|compound\tSylvana Beltrones , Manuel Añorve and Jorge Carlos Ramírez Marin|conj\tManuel Añorve and Jorge Carlos Ramírez Marin|conj\tJorge|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is Fabio Beltrones Rivera?",
                    "score": 0.7228,
                    "answers": "Fabio|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between the PRI, PVEM and NA?",
                    "score": 0.6957,
                    "answers": "For the PRI|prep\tthe PRI|pobj\tPVEM and NA|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Those who would be outside by the principle of relative majority would be the actress, Leticia Calderon (Green), Beatriz Pages, Jose Reyes Baeza and Cesar Camacho Quiroz.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Which actress was reported to be outside by the principle of relative majority?",
                    "answer": "Leticia Calderon"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What percentage of those who would be outside of the principle of relative majority would be undocumented immigrants?",
                    "score": 0.7498,
                    "answers": "of relative majority|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Leticia Calderon's political affiliation?",
                    "score": 0.6907,
                    "answers": "Green|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is Leticia Calderon?",
                    "score": 0.6381,
                    "answers": "www.eluniversal.com.mx reported on 03/07/2018 that Those who would be outside by the principle of relative majority would be the actress , Leticia Calderon ( Green ) , Beatriz Pages , Jose Reyes Baeza and Cesar Camacho Quiroz|ROOT\tthat|mark\twho|nsubj\twould|aux\tthe|det\twould|aux\tthe|det\tthe actress , Leticia Calderon ( Green ) , Beatriz Pages , Jose Reyes Baeza and Cesar Camacho Quiroz|attr\t,|punct\tLeticia|compound\tLeticia Calderon ( Green ) , Beatriz Pages , Jose Reyes Baeza and Cesar Camacho Quiroz|appos\t(|punct\t)|punct\t,|punct\t,|punct\tJose|compound\tand|cc"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is Leticia Calderon and Jose Reyes Baeza?",
                    "score": 0.6362,
                    "answers": "Beatriz|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is Cesar Camacho Quiroz?",
                    "score": 0.629,
                    "answers": "Cesar|compound"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "For the Senate of the Republic it is also necessary to calculate the trends to define the multi-nominal seats that each political party would obtain.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is another requirement for the Senate of the Republic?",
                    "answer": "calculate the trends to define the multi-nominal seats that each political party would obtain"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What trends are needed to determine the multi-nominal seats?",
                    "score": 0.8735,
                    "answers": "on 03/07/2018|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many seats does each political party obtain?",
                    "score": 0.8489,
                    "answers": "the multi - nominal seats that each political party would obtain|dobj\teach political party|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the trends to define the multi-nominal seats?",
                    "score": 0.831,
                    "answers": "to define the multi - nominal seats that each political party would obtain|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many seats would each political party obtain in the Senate of the Republic?",
                    "score": 0.8248,
                    "answers": "www.eluniversal.com.mx|nsubj\tthat For the Senate of the Republic it is also necessary to calculate the trends to define the multi - nominal seats that each political party would obtain|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the senate of the republic?",
                    "score": 0.7743,
                    "answers": "For the Senate of the Republic|prep\tof the Republic|prep"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}